Helm Stuart
(Sheldon:)-Hey.
-Sorry. Did I startle you?
(Stuart:)Yes, but at this point, pretty
much any customer does.
(Stuart:)-What can I do for you?
-Well, I need a little help.
(Bernadette:)I accidentally destroyed one of
Howard's comic books this morning,
(Bernadette:)-and was hoping I could replace it.
-Wow. What happened?
(Bernadette:)Batman got his ass kicked
by my curling iron.
(Stuart:)Don't let The Riddler know that.
(Stuart:)It's a comic book joke.
(Stuart:)Or maybe it's not.
(Bernadette:)-Do you have this one?
-Well, it's pretty rare.
(Stuart:)Can you give me a few
days to track it down?
(Bernadette:)I was kind of hoping to get it
before Howie comes home from work.
(Stuart:)-What's the hurry?
-Well, he's always saying
(Bernadette:)I should be more careful
with my curling iron,
(Bernadette:)and it seems like
a dangerous precedent
(Bernadette:)to let him think he can be right.
(Stuart:)Well, I'll do what I can,
but I can't make any promises.
(Bernadette:)You know, I do work
at a pharmaceutical company.
(Bernadette:)If you can make this happen today,